Guide to the Whitman College Vertical Files
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Whitman College Vertical Files Collection
approximately 1900-2018
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Whitman College. Whitman College and Northwest Archives
WCA.151
26 linear feet 16 filing cabinet drawers
The Whitman College Archives vertical file collection contains files pertaining to the history of Whitman College and people associated with the college.
Collection is open for research.
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
The Whitman College and Northwest Archives has maintained a vertical file about Whitman College since at least the 1960s. From the beginning, the purpose of the vertical file was to arrange and store small files on topics, memorabilia, and ephemeral material pertaining to Whitman College. For the most part, the vertical file contains only printed items. Manuscript material and other unique items were, generally, not placed in the vertical file. Some of the materials in the vertical file include: newspaper clippings, press releases, programs, speeches, reprints, and obituaries. Since the early 2000s, material has not been regularly added to the collection, but staff do occasionally add small additions.
The Whitman College Vertical Files collection contains subject files organized alphabetically by topic, department, or individual. Materials within include fliers, brochures, posters, publications, informational packets, reports, and biographical information on Whitman College, alumni, staff, faculty, departments, and general history.
- Abshire, Al
- Ackley, Charles
- Ackley, John W. Faculty 1934-45
- ACUC: Academic Computer Users' Committee
- Academic costume
- Activities and Rec. Team
- Acuff, M
- Adams, Kirk. '81 Student
- Adams, Kirk. '83
- Adamson, Walter (1975)
- Aden, Carlin. Alumni
- Adkison, Thomas. Architect.
- Adlington, Terry L.
- Advertising: Whitman College
- Aid to Scholarship and Instructional Development Committee
- Alcohol Awareness
- Alexander, Marilyn Maxey
- Alexander, Rodney Wilson. AB 1941, AM 1943, Faculty 1948-
- Alger, Michael
- Alkins, Jeanne
- Alkins, Mary
- Allard, David Henry. A.B. 1951
- Allen, Eli T. Obituary. (Wife: Mary Wallace Allen, see WW Union 9-17-34)
- Allen, Mary Gertrude Stockbridge (Mrs Orville Reid). Painted portrait of Narcissa Whitman.
- Allen, Raymond B. Dr. Honorary Sc.D. 1947
- Allen, Sir Richard. Faculty 1964-65.
- Allen, Thomas
- Allen, William
- Allender, Phoebe Jo.
- Alpha Chapter of Washington at Whitman College: diplomas for "Long Suffering Spouses of a Whitman College Enthusiast"
- Alsip, John F.
- Alumni House
- Ambrosia Hour
- American Civil Liberties Union
- America Reads Program
- Ames, John '61
- Amphitheater
- Amphitheater: Easter Sunrise Services, 1950. Buildings and Grounds.
- Amundsen, Dick
- Amnesty International
- Arnold Professors
- Anderson, Dr. Adele
- Anderson, Adele W. 1910-1997
- Anderson, Charles E. '50.
- Anderson, Edward F. Faculty 1962-1992
- Anderson, P. Geoffrey Gradebook 1887-89
- Anderson, Gordon
- Anderson Hall
- Anderson, H. Calvert "Cal"
- Anderson, Jennifer '88
- Anderson, Mark
- Andersen, Ross
- Anderson, William and Jeanie
- Anderson, Winslow Samuel President 1942-1948
- Andrews, David. Visiting Econ.
- Angell, H. Joseph
- Angell, Jimmye
- Ankeny, Nesmith C.
- Antenna Raise: Construction Applications
- Anthony, Paul Douglas
- Applegate, Dorothy. B.S. 1924
- Aravena, Rene
- Ardis, April. Dance.
- Arlington, David
- Armes, Norval (Verna)
- Armour, Richard
- Armstrong, Charles J. Dr. Faculty 1944-1953
- Armstrong, Dolores
- Arnold, Edward F.
- Arnold, Maurice
- Arnold, Lawrence
- Arnolds-Patron, Paul. Faculty.
- Arnold Professors
- Art Department
- Austen, Alpha
- Austin, Brian
- Auton, Betty
- Auton, Graeme P. Political Science.
- Arnquist, Warren Nelson. B.S. 1927, Ph.D. Calif. Inst. Tech '30
- Ayrault, Dan
- Backstrand, Winston C. Faculty.
- Back-to-Marc Festival
- Backus, Manson
- Bagley, Myrta. 1883
- Bail, George H.
- Bailey, William Horace Faculty 1946-?
- Baim, Michael. Visiting Asst. Prof., Chemistry
- Bainton, Roland Herbert. A.B. 1914
- Baird, Harold Leonard. Overseer.
- Baird, Lucius Olmsted
- Baird, Spencer Fullerton. Professorship.
- Baker, Crystal L. Visiting Instructor in Biology.
- Baker, Dorsey Franklin. Trustee. Hon. LL.D. '43
- Baker, Sarah (Mrs. W. P. Schwager)
- Baker, Walla Walla William. Seminary.
- Baldwin, E. D. 1906
- Baldwin, Ewart. Arnold Prof. 1981.
- Ball, George H., Whitman College Collection on.
- Ball, Nancy C.
- Ball, Robert S. '64; B. of T. 1992
- Ballard, Richard
- Banerjee, Dr. Purnendu Kumar. Litt.D. 1967.
- Banff Film Festival
- Barber, Joan.
- Barela, Mike '85 and Tracy Hill Barela '83
- Barken, Lenore. Asst. Prof. of Poli. Sci.
- Barker, Carol
- Barnett, Lindon.
- Barre, Arthur DeWitt
- Barrett, Newton. Alumni: 1914.
- Barrett, Parker. Overseer. B.S. 1903.
- Battelle Northwest
- Bauer, Marion E.
- Baxter, Margery
- Bean, Glenn Leonard
- Bean, Helen
- Bean, U. Grant.
- Beatty, Kathleen
- Beaulaurier, Elizabeth Ann
- Beaupre, D.F.
- Beaven, Corace May
- Beegle, David M.
- Beer, James M.
- Beezhold, Frank. Faculty 1938-
- Beidler, Joe
- Bells of Whitman College
- Bemis, Samuel Flagg. Faculty 1920-1923
- Bemrose, Paula. "Cookie Lady"
- Benedict, Dirk (Niewoehner). Grad. 1967.
- Benefits: College Insurance Benefit Plans
- Benjamin, Brown H.
- Bennett, Robert A. Faculty.
- Bennington, Virgil
- Benson, Germaine
- Benson, Michael
- Benzel, Mary
- Berelson, Bernard Reuben. A.B. 1934
- Berg, Charles H.
- Berge, Guttorm. 1954
- Berger, Sheila
- Bergvall, Dennis
- Bergevin, Erma Jo
- Berner, Ann Davis
- Berney, Charles. A.B. 1953
- Berney, Donald
- Berney, William E.
- Betournay, Judy
- Bettison-Varag, Lori
- Beus, Stephen
- Billings Hall
- Binkley, Joanne Gunn, Executive Secretary in Financial Development
- Birch, Anthony
- Birch, Tony, Controller 1980
- Birds in the Maxey Museum
- Bishop, Gayla
- Blakeslee, John. Visiting Ass't Prof. of Math
- Blankenship, Nancy; now Nancy Pryor. Alumni.
- Blankenship, Russell. Faculty 1923-1932
- Blankenship, Warren
- Blattler, Sarah R.
- Blanco, Pedro
- Bleakney, Walter. B.S. 1924
- Bleakney, William Hudson
- Bledsoe, Frances. Staff: __-1985
- Blomme, Gayle Barnes
- Blomquist, Arthur
- Blomquist, Roberta B. 1897-1988
- Blue Ridge Tutoring
- Blue Sky Program
- Blum - Music Association Pres.
- History of Whitman College boards developed for Edwards by Larry Dodd
- Boas, Ralph Phillip. Faculty 1912-1916
- Bodenberg, Emmett T. - Bio Prof.
- Bodvarsson, Orn
- Bohm, Fred
- Bonds, Christopher, Ph.D. 1975, Asst Prof of Music
- Bond, Grant S. 1904
- Borgensen, Mildred Shepherd
- Borleske Stadium
- Boals, Gordon Porter. A.B. 1926.
- Borseth, Jan
- Boule, Margie 1973
- Bowker, Lee H. Faculty 1967-
- Bowman, Mrs. Ruth. Asst. in Music
- Bown, Max Duane. Faculty 1941-1947
- Braden, Clarence. Overseer
- Bradford, Amanda - Student
- Bragg, Mrs. R.B. (Helen). News Service 1951-61
- Brittain, Margaret Elmina Teall
- Brann, Eva. Arnold Visiting Professor 1978-79
- Bratt, Gary - Dept of Music
- Bratton, Robert W.
- Bratton Tennis Center
- Bratton, Walter Andrew. Pres 1936-42, LLD 1942
- Bride, Howard
- Bridge Club
- Bridger, Clyde A. - A.B. 1931
- Breakaways
- Brode, Robert
- Brollier, Gordon 1988-91
- Broman, Cecily
- Broman, Walter - Prof. of English
- Brooking, Walter Jesse - A.B. 1934
- Brooks, Raymond Cummings - D.D. 1913
- Broughton, Ina Margaret - A.B. 1953
- Brown, Benjamin Harris - Faculty 1895-1935
- Brown, Carolyn Henning
- Brown, Dave
- Brown, Eli
- Brown, Geoffrey Wallace
- Brown, Greg
- Brown, Lisa
- Brown, Richard - Biology
- Brown, Roy Curtiss - Visiting Asst Professor of Biology - H. '76
- Brown, Sharon
- Brown, Zelma Williams
- Brubaker, Howard W. - Faculty 1904-1911
- Brunswig, Kirk
- Bryson, Blauke - '32
- Buck, Gayalene Norris, Food Service Director. H. 1977
- Buchanan, Martin
- Buckley, Chester W. - Faculty 1961-
- Budget - 40 years of Balanced Budgets
- Budget
- Buehler, Elizabeth Wilson - 1942
- Buffo, Lauren
- Bunnell, Jodi L.
- Bunnell, John C.
- Bunnell, Rod and Sally
- Bunt, Floyd Walter - staff
- Burge, David - Faculty 1957-
- Burgess, Dana - Prof of Foreign Lang. and Lit - Classics
- Burgess, Dr. M. Elaine
- Burgess, Esther - German
- Burgess, Robert - Faculty
- Burke, Kevin - visiting math prof
- Burk, Richard - Visiting Prof. of Drama 1983-84
- Burke, Thomas - L.L.D. 1898
- Burman, Tom - Speech at Founder's Day at Whitman College, February, 1985
- Burman, Thomas
- Burns, Margaret
- Buroker, Usona
- Burr, Helen L
- Burton, Patricia - visiting prof. of philosophy
- Busch, Neal - Chemistry
- Business Office
- Busch, Robert - Visiting Lecturer in Biology
- Buss, Paul A. Jr
- Bussard, Lawrence Harold - Faculty 1943-1951
- Butler, Preston
- Butterworth, Rev. F.E. - Hon. Degree
- Byers, Deborah - class of 1986
- Cabin (Soda Fountain) 1943
- College Cabin Mill Creek
- Cain, Leslie
- Cain, Llewellyn B.
- Cain, William
- Camp Whitman
- Cameron, Basil: Honorary Degree: Doctor of Music, 2-14-35
- Campbell, Allison: Lecturer in Chemistry
- Campbell, Carl: Faculty 1960-
- Campbell, David Beasley: Former Instr. In Piano
- Campbell, Gay: Director of News Services
- Campbell, Mary Thorne: 1933
- Campbell, Tim
- Campus Art
- Campus Conference on Religion 1949-60
- Cannon, Garnett E.: Overseer
- Campus Day Program
- Campus sculpture walking tour, 2018
- Carloye, Lisa
- Carnegie Report
- Carson, Bob
- Carcamo, Roberto
- Carlsen, Douglas
- Carlstrom, Connie Jill 1993
- Carpenter, Sandra Witt
- Carloye, Lisa
- Carnegie Report
- Carson, Robert J.
- Castile File
- Castile, George: Faculty 1972-
- Cassens, Dorothy 1931
- Catering Services
- Celebrations (Graduation, Alumni Reunions)
- Cell Group Program
- Celt House
- Chamberlaw, Dave
- Cassinelli, Charles W., Faculty 1953-1960
- Cathcart, Kevin
- Center for Community Service
- Chamberlain, Mark
- Chamberlain, P.B.
- Chamberlin, Marilyn
- Chan, Roger: Vis. Instr. Of History
- Chastain, W. J.
- Chapel - Faculty-student joint committee report 1929
- Chapman, Raymond L.
- Cheatham, James
- Chen, C. Lon: Asst. Prof. of Economics
- Chesney, Margaret
- Chiarelott, Donna (News Services)- 2 Folders
- Chiarelott, Leigh
- Chief Information Technology Officer: New Position 1993
- Chinese Exhibit - 1984
- Chinese House
- Chinese Students
- Churchill, Joan: Assoc. Prof. of Theatre
- Chorale
- Chronicle of Higher Education
- Circle K, (Service Club)
- Cinema Arts Series
- Clark, Curtis
- Class Representatives Handbook
- Classic Film Series
- Claytor, Elma L.: RN Health Center, 1962
- Clayton, Dr. E.
- Clem, Richard H.
- Clemens, Fred W. 1911
- Clemen, Rudolf Alexander
- Clendaniel, Ed
- Clercx, Byron: Visiting Prof. of Studio Art
- Click, Sally - Asst. Dean of Students
- Click, William
- Climbing Wall: Sherwood Center
- Cline, Alvin: Faculty
- Clippings - WC, General
- Clodius, Robert L.
- Clow, Maurine
- Coates, Cushing Eells
- Cochrane, Kevin D.: Class of 1979
- Co-Educational Living
- Cockrum, Virginia
- Coddington, Barbara
- Coffee House
- Cohee, Brian: Class of 1986
- Cohen, Mark
- Cohen, Ronald D.
- Cole, Bill: 1972 Humanities Chair
- Cole, Donald C.
- Cole, Douglas Lowell
- Cole, William
- Coleman, Norman Frank: Faculty
- Colors, Whitman
- College House
- Collegiate Political Organizations
- Coffeehouse Posters
- Colligan, Karen: Instructor in Foreign Languages
- Collins, Joan
- Columbine Players, WC collection on, summer stock theatre program
- Committee - Internship
- Conner, Liz: Sub Snack Bar Manager
- Community Free School
- Community Food Cooperative (co-op)
- Comegys
- Computer: IBM
- Computer Service
- Computer Use Policy
- Conferences, Conventions, Meetings: 2 Folders
- Coon, Roberta
- Conklin, Loni
- Connell, Carl
- Conrad, Vernon
- Conry, Catherine
- Cook, Jonathan and Elizabeth
- Copeland, Frances Virginia
- Copeland, Henry J.: Overseer
- Copeland, Paul W.
- Copeland, Laura
- Copeland, Mary Penrose
- Copeland, Paul W.
- Conferences: Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1960
- Conferences: Governing Board, 1960
- Conference, Greater Whitman: 1960
- Conferences: Model Conferences, Conventions
- Conferences: Pioneer Trails, 1953
- Conservation Committee
- Construction
- Controller
- Cordiner, Glen
- Cordiner, Lee
- Cordiner, Ralph
- Corey, Douglas
- Corkille Briggs, Dorothy
- Corley, Peggy
- Cornelison, Mary Jane
- Cornish, Rory
- Cormier, Lee D.: Conservatory
- Corrigan, Marilyn J.
- Cosby, Judith
- Cosgrove, Anthony
- Costas, P.S.: Faculty
- Cottie, Charles Sidney
- Cottrell, Ted
- Cottrell, Walter and Christine
- Councils and Committees
- Counseling Center
- Cousins, Mrs. Lawrence
- Cowles
- Cowling, H. Miller
- Cox, Cody
- Cox, Manning William
- Cox, Robert West
- Coyne, Barry
- Crawford, Harold
- Crayne, Mrs. W.H.
- Creegan, Robert F.
- Crisp, Wendy Reid
- Crocker, Ryan
- Crocker, Sewall King
- Cross, Rt. Rev. Edward
- Crowe, William Frank
- Cruchon, Janine
- Crumbaker, Calvino
- Cummins, L.W. "Scotty"
- Cundiff, Jerry Sr.
- Cunningham,Jonathan Ray
- Curcio, Louis
- Curley, David W.
- Currie, Peggy
- Curtis, Jerry
- Cryptography
- Cycling Team
- Dagle, Gerald
- Dale, Harrison Clifford
- Dana, Marshall Newport
- Dambacher, George
- Dance Studio
- Danelski, David J.
- Daniel, Inez
- Dappan, Andy
- Darlington, Wayne
- Davenport, H.T. (Margaret Paddock)
- Davidman, Leonard
- Davis, Edith B.M.
- Davis, Julia
- Davis, Frederic
- Davis, Kenneth Culp
- Davis, Merrell R.
- Davis, W.R.
- Davis, Mrs. W.R.
- Davis, Wallace Martin
- Daycare at Whitman (proposals)
- Dean & Burgett (Ray & Grace) photograph album (photocopy), circa 1920
- Dean of Faculty
- Dean of Students
- Dean, Mary Evelyn
- Deeringhoff, Lori
- DeLaney, John E.
- Delay, Ron
- Delta Delta Delta
- Demaris, Steve
- Demaris, Tom
- Dennis, Johnnie
- Dennis, Kevin
- DeRemer, Russell J.
- Deshler, William
- Deval, Anne-Marie
- Development
- Dewey, Michele
- Deye, Ruth
- Dick, Wesley Arden
- Dianisus
- Dignitary Dinner
- Diller, Karen
- Dimond, Thomas M.
- Dingee, Eugene
- Distribution
- Diven, Clarence
- Dixon, Edward
- Dixon, Jerry
- Dobson, Heidi
- Dodson, Craig
- Doebler, Dawn Elisa
- Doherty, Barbara B.
- Donahie, Dan
- Donaldson, Timothy
- Dormitory Regulations
- Dorr, Angelika
- Douglas, Bob
- Dory, Jenise
- Douglas, Arthur Freeborn
- Douglas, Mildred Riddle
- Douglas, Martha
- Douglas, Leigh C.
- Dovell, William Thomas
- Downing, Elaine
- Downs, C. R
- Dox, Virginia
- Drabek, Charles
- Drake, Barbara
- Drake, Robert
- Draper, Gordon
- Driscoll, James P.
- Drug Awareness Committee
- Drury, Clifford Merrill
- Dubost, Francoise
- Duck Fest, Annual
- Duckham, W. Henry
- Duffin, Mark
- Dunphy, Sabina
- Dunphy, W.T.
- Dunphy, Winifred
- Dunlap
- Dunning, John Ray
- Durand, Paul A.
- Ealy, Laura
- Easton, Stanly Alexander
- Eaton, Rev. James Francis
- Education Programs
- Edwards, Bert
- Edwards, Stephanie
- Edwards, Jack
- Edwards, Glenn Thomas
- Edwards, Jonathan Whitman
- Edwards, Rosine M.
- Edwards, Stephanie
- Edwards, Todd
- Egau, James
- Egolf-Sham Rao, Cindy
- Ehni, Walter
- Elbert, Chris M.
- Ellertson, Jessica
- Ellertson, Chris
- Ellis, Harold
- Ellis, Whitney
- Elmore, Richard F.
- Elshin, Jacob
- Ely, Carol
- Emerson, William
- Erickson
- Engdahl, Frank Edmiston
- Esary, Craig
- Esary, J.D.
- Esary, Janet Richardson
- Estassi, Shukri
- Evans, Dan
- Even, Jeff
- Whitman Express
- Extern Program
- Extracurricular Activities, Student Life
- Facilities Resourse Management Co.
- Faculty Email
- New Faculty
- Faculty, New and Visiting
- Faculty Development Office
- Faculty Forum
- Faculty Fun Committee
- Faculty 1995-96
- New Faculty 1990-91
- Faculty 1996-97
- Faculty Professorships
- Faculty 1994-95
- Faculty 1993-94
- General Faculty 1992-94
- Faculty Misc.
- Faculty, General 1992-93
- Faculty, General
- General Faculty 1990-91
- General Faculty 1989-90
- General Faculty 1988-89
- General Faculty 1987-88
- General Faculty 1986-87
- General Faculty 1985-86
- Geneal Faculty 1984-85
- General Faculty 1983-84
- General Faculty 1982-83
- General Faculty Before 1982
- Faculty: Sabbaticals
- Faculty: Speakers Bureau
- Faculty Tenure
- Fahey, M.
- Fair Labor Standards Act
- Fairbank, Bill and Jane
- Family Weekend
- Fargo, Lucille Foster
- Farmer, Sam J.
- Farnsworth, E.L.
- Farris, Michael
- Farrington, Keith (2 folders)
- Fawcett, Sherwood L.
- Fee, James Alger
- Fencing
- Fenik, Bernard C. Visiting Johnston Professor of Classics
- Ferguson, Baker
- Ferris, Joel Edward
- Ferris, Joel E.
- Ferguson, Frances P.
- Ferguson, Jesse
- Fatters, Marvin
- Field Naturalists Club
- Fifield, Wendell
- Fifield, Wendell
- Filla, Darlene
- Films
- Finkas, Ralph C.
- Fischer, Edward
- Flemming, Arthur Sherwood
- Fletcher, Eugene
- Fly Fishing Club
- Fogarty, Joseph Jerry
- Fogle, James L.
- Fogarty, Jerry
- Foley, Thomas Stephen
- Fontera, Richard M.
- Ford, Paul M.
- Forensics
- Forsyth, John Bailey
- Foster, Dorothy
- Foster, Edward
- Forester, Aarom
- Founder's Day
- Fowler, William Archibald
- Francis, Mark
- Frazier, Neta Lohnes
- Frease, Dean E.
- French House
- French, Dr. C. Clement
- Freshman Life Committee
- Frey, Mrs. Sophia
- Fringe Benefit Committee
- Frisbee, Donald C.
- Frisbee Golf
- Fun Runs
- Fusser's Guide
- Gainer, Mildred
- Gaiser Reunion
- Gaiser, Dr. David Wesley
- Gaiser, Mary Cooper Jewett
- Gaiser Family
- Gallagher, Marion Gould
- Galbraith, Nettie M.
- Gamon, Margaret
- Garfield, Harry Augustus
- Garland, "B"
- Garrecht, Francis A.
- Garrett, Gerald Robert
- Garrett, Paul Willard (see scholarship)
- Garrettson, Albert Henry
- Garrison, Phyllis L.
- Lindy Hardy, Idaho High Schools
- General Information, Whitman College
- George, Ralph E.
- Geppert, Heinz Wolfgang
- Gerfen, Maya
- German House (2 files)
- Gibbons, Ada
- Gilliam, Jackson
- Gilliland, Lisa Kim
- Gilmour, John J.
- Givins, Ellen
- Glenny, Alta I.
- Gleam, Elfreda
- Glenny, Alta
- Glick, Dr. Paul C. (faculty)
- Global Problem Committee
- Goertz, Jason
- Good, Trafford Ross
- Goodman, Linda
- Goodman, David M.
- Goodwin, Robert Clifford
- Gordon, Hattie
- Gordon, Ron
- Gose, Judge Mack F.
- Gose, John Gordon
- Gowen, Herbert Henry
- Graduation Pledge of Environmental and Social Responsibility, 1999
- Graff, Anne Colver
- Graffiti
- Graham, Harold
- Graham, Margaret Bill
- Graham, Robert Weston
- Graham, David Crockett
- Grant, Bill
- Gray, Newton M.
- Green, Reginald
- Green, Reginald Herbold
- Green, Reginald James
- Greene, Neva '1912
- Greenfield, Peter
- Greenslade, William Gaius
- Gregg, Emma Stine
- Gregg, Gennie
- Gregg, Mrs. H.C.
- Gregoire, Cindy
- Griffen, Larry
- Griffen, Marisa
- Gose, Margaret
- Gray, Dan
- Grigsby, Marcy
- Grove, Mrs. Edna
- Guernsey, William
- Whitman Guild
- Gulick, Dr. Luther H.
- Gunson, Karen
- Gunn, Pearl
- Hadley, Herschell
- Hahn, Rev. Clement
- Haigh, Frank Loyal
- Haigh, John W.
- Hailston, Oakley
- Haines, Charles Grove
- Haines, Jim
- Hale, David F.
- Hale, Mrs. Oron J.
- Hall, Ada R.
- Haller, Charles D.
- Hamilton
- Hampson, Thomas
- Hansberger, R.V.
- Whitman Graduates- Election 1996
- Hansell, Stafford
- Hanson, Eugene
- Hanson, Franklin "Pete"
- Hara, Keiko
- Harbach, Otto
- Harber, Patricia
- Harbold, William
- Hardy, Linda
- Harmon, Lloydina
- Harris, Elizabeth
- Hartley, Jamie
- Hartung Beverly Jean
- Hartz, Carolyn
- Harvey, Paul
- Hauerback, Otto A.
- Hawman, Arthur
- Heath, Jennifer
- Heilman, Robert B.
- Helm, Hilary
- Hemsing, Peter
- Henderson, Shannon
- Hendrick, A.W.
- Henkles, John B.
- Hennger, Mike
- Henry, Geraldine Howard
- Herbert, Margaretta
- Herring, Bruce
- Hetzel, Howard R.
- Hiefield, Matthew J
- Highberg, Ann
- Highber, Ivan Edmund
- Hill, Howard William
- Hill, James Scott
- Hill, Traci Lyn
- Hill, Dr. Rolla Bennett
- Hillel-Shalom, Jewish Student Group
- Hillis, Jerry
- Himmelright, Robert S.
- Hine, Steven
- Hinkley, Edith Smaw
- Hitchman, J.H.
- Hockett, Dorothy
- Hodel, David
- Hodgson, H. Joan
- Hoerlein, Diana L.
- Hofer, George P.
- Hofius, Philip 2012
- Holland, Helen Britton
- Holiday Program
- Holmes, Lulu
- Holmes, Lulu Haskell
- Holmstrand, James
- Holmes, Otil Hal
- Holmstrand, James
- Holt, Wayne (2 Folders)
- Homecomings
- Homecoming: 1968
- Homecoming: 1966
- Homecoming: 1991
- Homecoming: 1995
- Homecoming: 1997
- Homecoming and Parents Weekend
- Hong, Laraine K.N.
- Hongate, Lola
- Honoraries
- Honorary Degrees
- Hooa, Kinby Grant
- Hoornbeck, Paul
- Hoover, Roy W.
- Hopkinson, Deborah
- Horvath, Janos
- Hosokawa, Robert R.
- Howard, Charles Wilber
- Howard, Ella
- Howe, Ruel Lanphier
- Howell, Christopher
- Howells, Ada
- Hower, Kelly (Mark)
- Howland, L.P.
- Hoyt, Edwin Palmer
- Hsuan-Chun, Lin
- Hughes, R.H.
- Hull, Joe
- Humphrys Edward
- Humphrey, Leo Chandler
- Humphrey, Louise
- Hunt, Bradley Jay
- Huntington, Jack
- Huntley, Wade
- Hussey, Larry
- Hutchings, Dr. Phyllis (2 Folders)
- Hutchings, Dr. William L.
- Hutson-Fish, Idalee
- I Have A Dream Program hosted at Whitman
- Imhoff, Guy
- Immer, Stephen C.
- Inaugurations
- Ingraham, G.F.
- Instructional Media
- Intercollege Mock Political Convention
- Irwin, Hugh
- Irwin, Marion
- Iverson, Iver
- Admin files of Lary Beaulaurier (?), Alumni Fundraising and Annual Fund Records
- Jackson, Greg
- Jackson, Senator Henry M.
- Jackson, Henry M.
- Jackson, Paul J.
- Jackson, Manion
- Jackson, Nagle
- Jacobs, Hayes B.
- Jacobs, Melvin Clay
- Jacobson, Donald J.
- Janson, Leonard Francis (3 Folders)
- Jamieson, Dean
- Japanese Garden
- Jarboe, Pam
- Jaynes, Gordon Leslie
- Jennings, Shirley Anderson
- Jernigon, Ann
- Jervis, Thomas
- Jeske, Timothy D.
- Jesseph, H.E. "Jerry"
- Jeucks, Bradford
- Jewett, George Frederick
- Johns, James Shanard
- Johnson, Edson
- Johnson, Jean, Photograph Executive Secretary 1980
- Johnson, Jean
- Johnson, Holly
- Johnson, Lloyd P.
- Johnson, Mrs. Lowden
- Johnson, Marion
- Johnson, Max G.
- Johnson, Sarah
- Johnston, Denis
- Johnston, Eric A.
- Johnston, Stuart and Joyce
- Johnston, Suzanne
- Johstone, Malcolm
- Jones, Evan
- Jones, Dwelly Sr.
- Jones, Gerwyn
- Jones, Howard M.
- Jones, Joan
- Jones, Kathryn
- Jones, Marianna
- Jones, Mary
- Jones, Nettie
- Jonish, Arley
- Jordan, Beatrice Cockram (2 folders)
- Jorgenson, Bud
- Jorre, Ronald M.
- Joseph III, Gabe
- Joy, Annie L.
- Judd, Mary Diver
- Jue, Brian J.
- Kafoury, Deborah
- Kajita, Mark H.
- Kafoury, Gretchen Miller
- Kaminsky, Eric
- Kanakey, Jill
- Kaplan, Richard
- Kasza, Gregory
- Katthain, Angelina
- Kautz, Betty Jean
- Kees, Marion
- Keiser, Victor H.
- Kelly, John Grant
- Kelley, Eugene A.
- Kelley, Win
- Kelling, Lucille
- Kelsey, Sigrid Thompson
- Kennedy, Betty Lou
- Kenner, Carolyn
- Kennewick Man
- Kerns, James Alexander
- Kerns, Thomas D.
- Kicker, Leroy
- Kight, Grace M.
- Kilkenny, John
- Kimball, Ruth
- Kincaid, Charles
- Kids Place
- 1977 and End of Football
- King, Roger
- Kingman, Shareen
- Kinsinger, Helen
- Kinsinger, Vern
- Kirkman, Fanny A.
- Kirkman, John Shaw
- Kenworthy, Eldon
- Kirkman, Robert H.
- Kirsher, Himer Benjamin
- Klein, Joanne
- County Law and Justice Committee
- Klicker, David
- Knight of the Living Eggplant
- Knostman, Paul Journal
- Knott, Howard James
- Knox, Warren B.
- Kodros, Archie
- Koenig, Dixie
- Koenninger, Robin
- Kohler, Martin L. Jr.
- Kopf, Martin
- Korgan, Michelle. Student opens Pangea coffee shop
- Kovac, Kim Peter
- Krieg, Al
- Kristianson, Andrew Evans
- Kroesch, Samuel
- Kuhl, Sarah J.
- Kutsky, Diana
- KWCW: Desert isle show by Dana Leighton (invites: Dayna Erickson and Tom Cronin)
- Kvam, Robert
- Kyoto Program
- Laidlaw, Dr. Melvern E.
- Lager, Patrick
- Laing, Ellen
- Lake (College Creek and Lakum Duckum)
- Lakey, Othal H.
- Lalovic, Ivan and Miso Mitkovski
- Lamb, Frank G.
- Lamb, Lois
- Lambe, Dean R.
- Lambert, Jon R.
- "The Lament of a Whitman Spouse"
- Lancefield, Hilda Marguerite
- Lane, Scott and Lalitha
- Lane, Stephen
- Lang, William L.
- Lange, Ned
- Larsen, Russell
- Larisch, Sharon
- Larson, Cleve
- Larson, Debra
- Laslett, Herbert R.
- Lazarson, Grace
- LEAD